As a dog lover, our canine companions always fill me with joy.
作为一个爱狗人士，我们的犬类（canine）伙伴总是让我满心欢喜。
Whether pedigree or mongrel, tame or stray, whenever I see one, I smile.
无论是纯种狗（pedigree）还是混血狗（mongrel），温顺的还是流浪的，每当我看到一只狗，我都会微笑。
After all, their loyalty is indisputable, their companionship is always welcome, they fetch for us, guard for us and even work for us when required.
毕竟，它们的忠诚是无可争议的（indisputable），它们的陪伴总是令人欣然接受的，它们为我们叼东西，为我们看家，甚至在需要的时候为我们工作。
Good old Fido has always been close to my, and many other’s hearts.
可爱的老狗狗一直深受我和许多人的喜爱。
Well, not content with just warming the cockles of your heart, it seems that our four-legged-friends actually lower the risk of cardiovascular disease, according to a 2017 scientific study, which looked at 3.4 million Swedes from 2001 to 2012.
嗯，我们的这些四条腿的朋友们可不满足于仅仅温暖你的内心深处，根据2017年的一项科学研究，它们实际上还能降低心血管（cardiovascular）疾病的风险。这项研究对2001年至2012年间的340万瑞典人进行了调查。
The study concluded that this lower risk, which was particularly evident in owners of hunting breeds, may not just be due to the increased physical activity that goes hand-in-hand with owning a dog, but could also be down to dogs increasing the owner’s social contact, or by changing the owner's bacterial microbiome, which is the collection of microscopic species that live in the gut.
研究得出结论，这种风险的降低在猎犬的主人身上尤为明显，这可能不仅仅是因为和狗同行会增加身体活动量，还可能归因于（down to）狗狗增加了主人的社交接触，或者改变了主人的细菌微生物群（bacterial microbiome），也就是生活在肠道内的微观物种的集合。
Dogs change the dirt in home environments and therefore expose people to bacteria that they would otherwise not encounter.
狗狗会改变家庭环境中的尘埃，因此会让人们接触到原本不会遇到的细菌。
These effects were particularly marked in those who lived on their lonesome.
这些影响在那些独自（lonesome）生活的人身上尤为显著。
According to Mwenya Mubanga of Uppsala University and lead author of the study, “single dog owners had a 33% reduction in risk of death and an 11% reduction in risk of cardiac arrest compared to single non-owners.”
根据乌普萨拉大学（Uppsala University）的姆温亚・穆班加（Mwenya Mubanga），也就是这项研究的第一作者所说：“与没有养狗的单身人士相比，养狗的单身人士死亡风险降低了33%，心脏骤停的风险降低了11%。”
However, before your heart skips a beat, Tove Fall, senior author of the study, also adds that there may be limitations.
然而，在你感到开心兴奋之前，这项研究的资深作者托芙・法尔（Tove Fall）也补充说，可能存在一些局限性。
It’s possible that the differences between owners and non-owners, which already existed before the dog was bought, could have influenced the results – or that people who are generally more active also tend to get a dog anyway.
有可能在购买狗之前，养狗者和不养狗者之间已经存在的差异就有可能已经影响了研究结果——或者那些通常更活跃的人无论如何也更倾向于养狗。
It seems that the results are not as clear cut as they initially appear to be, but as far as I’m concerned, that’s ok.
似乎研究结果并不像最初看起来那样明确（clear cut），但就我而言，这没关系。
I love dogs for how they make me feel and, cardiovascular benefits or not, they’ll always be top dog to me – cross my heart.
我爱狗是因为它们给我的感觉，而且不管有没有心血管方面的益处，它们在我心中永远都是最重要的（top dog）——我发誓。